{
  "Q653": {
    "entity": "entity",
    "results": [
      {
        "question": "What is the origin of the Chihuahua breed of dog?",
        "answer": "Mexico."
      },
      {
        "question": "How small is the Chihuahua compared to other dog breeds?",
        "answer": "Chihuahuas are among the smallest of all dog breeds."
      },
      {
        "question": "What percentage of Chihuahuas have a unique genetic signature?",
        "answer": "Approximately 4% of Chihuahuas have a unique genetic signature."
      },
      {
        "question": "What did Hernan Cort\u00e9s write about the Aztecs and Chihuahuas?",
        "answer": "Hernan Cort\u00e9s wrote that the Aztecs raised and sold Chihuahuas as food."
      },
      {
        "question": "When was the first Chihuahua registered by the American Kennel Club?",
        "answer": "The first Chihuahua was registered by the American Kennel Club in 1904."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the preferred weight for a Chihuahua in conformation shows?",
        "answer": "Ideally between 1.5 and 3.0 kg (3.3 and 6.6 lbs)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can Chihuahuas weigh more than 10 lb (4.5 kg)?",
        "answer": "Yes, if they have large bone structures or become overweight."
      },
      {
        "question": "Do oversized Chihuahuas exist in certain bloodlines?",
        "answer": "Yes, oversized Chihuahuas can be found in both good and bad bloodlines."
      },
      {
        "question": "Do Chihuahuas breed true for size?",
        "answer": "No, puppies from the same litter can mature in different sizes."
      },
      {
        "question": "Are larger breeding females less likely to experience obstructed labor?",
        "answer": "Yes, larger breeding females have a lower risk of dystocia."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the reason some breeders try to make Chihuahuas smaller?",
        "answer": "\"Teacup\" or \"tiny teacup\" Chihuahuas demand higher prices."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why did The Kennel Club decide not to register merle Chihuahuas?",
        "answer": "Merle coat pattern in Chihuahuas is associated with health risks."
      },
      {
        "question": "Do Chihuahuas have a higher tendency for aggression compared to other dogs?",
        "answer": "Yes, Chihuahuas may display above-average aggression towards people and other dogs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are some neurological diseases that Chihuahuas are genetically predisposed to?",
        "answer": "Atlantoaxial instability, ceroid lipofuscinosis, congenital deafness, and more."
      },
      {
        "question": "How long is the average lifespan of a Chihuahua?",
        "answer": "A Chihuahua may live for twelve years or more."
      }
    ]
  }
}